[Music]
When business experiences a problem with
the integration between the front end
Shopify and back end Business Central,
it is important to quickly find the root
cause and different levels of logging
helps to reduce time needed to
investigate and solve the problem. Let's
see it in action.
In this scenario, customer data will be
exported as a Shopify company. When
exporting data to Shopify, the Shopify
connector skips records if they are
invalid for export or likely to be
rejected by
Shopify. During synchronization, a
notification about skipped records
appears. Choose view skipped records to
open the Shopify skipped records page.
There is an entry indicating an email is
missing, which is a required field.
Choose show record to open customer card
page and confirm the email field is
empty. This needs to be
corrected. Before closing the page,
notice other examples related to items
or sales invoice
exports. After fixing the customer
record, export it successfully.
The functionality is controlled by the
logging mode field. Both all and error
only activate logging of skipped
entries. Thank you for watching. You can
find additional details about this
capability in the release note. Also
check other videos about other Shopify
enhancements. You can find links in the
description.